James Rivett

jrivett@students.kennesaw.edu (678) - 997 - 7749 james-rivett.com

Profile

After eighteen months interning with a global leader in Financial Tech, my entire experience can be summarized in one statement: There will always be an opportunity to learn. My goal is not only to make notable contributions, but to deepen and broaden my proficiencies while doing so. While the following list does outline my current skillset, it also serves as a testament to how quickly I can expand it.

Education

Kennesaw State University

B.S. | Computer Science August 2018 - December 2022

Related Experience

DevOps Intern | InComm Payments | April 2021 - Present

- Served development teams in a fast-paced release environment by implementing CI/CD pipelines in multiple Jenkins instances
- Enhanced those pipelines by providing specialized functionality such as approval gates and static code scanning with tools such as Snyk
- Wrote and maintained a wide variety of tools and library functions in the Groovy programming language ranging from success/failure email notifications to safe mass deletion scripts for cleanup
- Implemented Self-Hosted GitHub Action Runners to automatically trigger CI pipelines

Electric Vehicle Team | Kennesaw State University | August 2022 - Present

- Maintained a complex docker workspace and provided cross-platform UI functionality using VNC
- Utilized Robot Operating System (ROS2) to enable our mechanical team with empirical data for testing
- Served as a medium between minds of many different proficiencies by translating low-level ideas into high-level English that everyone in the room understands

Freelance Designer | 2014 - 2021

- Created unique branding and outreach for clientele ranging from small startups to large corporations
- Published an expansive portfolio of personal artwork made using Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop

Skills

Tools/Software

Docker, Jenkins, Linux, Adobe CC, GitHub Actions, Azure

Programming/Scripting Languages

Bash, Groovy, Python, C++, Rust, Java, HTML/CSS/JS, C#